we just finished episode number 413 I'm
لقد انتهينا للتو من رقم الحلقة 413
just sitting in the studio parking lot
مجرد الجلوس في موقف للسيارات الاستوديو
and I can't even pull out because my the
وأنا لا أستطيع حتى الانسحاب لأن بلدي
storm is so bad can't even see out the
العاصفة سيئة للغاية لا يمكن حتى رؤية
windows so I'm just going to kind of
ويندوز لذلك أنا ذاهب الى نوع من
wait for a minute oh my goodness those
انتظر لحظة يا الله
who were in the chat were just after the
الذين كانوا في الدردشة كانوا فقط بعد
show well you know at the end of the
تظهر بشكل جيد كما تعلم في نهاية
show I said it's looking like a bit of a
عرض قلت انها تبدو وكأنها جزء من
storm out there and then it got really
العاصفة هناك ثم حصلت حقا
bad we've got one window that is letting
سيئة لدينا نافذة واحدة تركت
some water in so I put a bowl there and
بعض الماء في ذلك وضع وعاء هناك و
I'll have to come back when when things
سآخذ للعودة عندما عندما الأمور
settle down and get that taken care of
يستقر والحصول على تلك العناية
figure out what's going on there
معرفة ما يجري هناك
probably just a little bit of caulking
ربما فقط القليل من السد
or something but yeah this is what it
أو شيء ما ولكن نعم هذا ما هو عليه
looks like here after episode number 413
يبدو هنا بعد الحلقة رقم 413
you can't even probably tell
لا يمكنك حتى أن تقول
it's nasty
انها سيئة
fine and hopefully soon I'll be able to
بخير ونأمل قريبا سأتمكن من ذلك
pull out everybody else made it out just
سحب الجميع جعله خارجا فقط
as it was starting everybody got soaked
كما بدأ الجميع ينقع
but I'm absolutely drenched try to get
ولكن أنا غارق تماما في محاولة للحصول عليها
the equipment out and and in the van
المعدات و و في الشاحنة
safely added a couple rent anyways
بأمان إضافة زوجين الإيجار على أي حال
thanks for tuning in and thanks for
شكرا لضبط وشكر ل
watching category 5 TV I'm going to get
مشاهدة فئة 5 TV انا ذاهب للحصول عليها
it going once the windows clear up
تسير بمجرد أن النوافذ واضحة
starting there we go almost see-through
ابتداء من هناك نذهب تقريبا نرى من خلال
anyways take care I'll see you soon bye
على أي حال احرص سأراكم قريبا
I was just about to pull out and this is
كنت على وشك الانسحاب وهذا هو
not good we have a ditch on either side
ليس جيدا لدينا خندق على كلا الجانبين
of our driveway and it is so full of
من دربنا وهو مليء جدا
water I can't tell where the ditches and
الماء لا استطيع ان اقول اين الخنادق و
where the driveway is it just looks like
حيث درب هو يبدو تماما مثل
soul and all the way across I'm going to
الروح وعلى طول الطريق عبر أنا ذاهب ل
have to step out see
يجب أن تخرج
ah
آه
oh it's like a foot deep
يا مثل القدم العميق
standing in a foot of water and that's
يقف في سفح من الماء وهذا
happening
حدث
holy crap
تبا
please
رجاء
oh man
يا رجل
I mean
انا اعني
I am glad that I'm able to stay on high
أنا سعيد لأنني قادر على البقاء على أعلى مستوى
ground there are some people who would
الأرض هناك بعض الناس من شأنه
have been going home
تم الذهاب المنزل
areas a lot of hills
المناطق الكثير من التلال
and if you have to go down one of these
وإذا كان عليك أن تنزل واحدة من هذه
hills to get up to where you live I
التلال للوصول إلى المكان الذي تعيش فيه أنا
don't even want to think about how much
لا أريد حتى أن التفكير في مدى
water there is down
الماء هناك
an email everybody make sure they got
والجميع البريد الإلكتروني تأكد من أنهم وصلوا
home safe
منزل آمن